Guide to the Elsie H. Hillman Papers, 1920-2015 AIS.2013.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Republican Party Activity, 1960-2000; I.
  - Republican National Conventions, 1960-2000; 2.
    - 35th Republican National Convention, Houston, Texas, 1992
      - Prohibited Items, Memorandum, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - RNC Gala, Program, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Republican National Committee Member Identification, Memorandum, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Republican National Committee Summer Meeting, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Ripon Society, Convention Press, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Rules, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Schedule and Seating Chart, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Standing Committee Meetings, Tentative Schedule, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - A Tribute to First Lady Barbara Bush, Program, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - A Tribute to First Lady Barbara Bush, Tickets, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Unity Platform '92, Project Outline, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Welcome Letter, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 36th Republican National Convention, San Diego, California, 1996
      - Allocation of Credentials, Tickets, and Badges, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Arrival Times, Memorandum, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Call for the 1996 Republican National Convention (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - "A Celebration of Leadership: A Listing of State and Federal Elected Republican Women", 1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Committee for a Conservative Platform Booklet, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Committee on Arrangements, Memorandum, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Convention Guide for Republican Eagles, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Bob Gleason to Bob Dole, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Elsie Hillman to Florence Bridges regarding Dole's remarks at the Convention, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Tim Shaffer to Elsie Hillman, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Delegates, Alternate Delegates and Guest Lists, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Delegates, Delegate Tracking, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Delegates, List of Friendly Delegates, Alternates, and Guests, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Delegation Whips and Runners, Notes and Guidelines, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 22)
      - Handwritten Schedule and Daily Activity Sheets, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Hawaiian Luau (sponsored by Hillman), Invitation, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Interfaith Alliance, Interfaith Prayer Rally, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Invitations, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Media Contact Information, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Official Report of the Proceedings (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Op-Eds and Articles, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Order of Business, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 31)
      - Parliamentary Tactics Action Plan, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 32)
      - Pennsylvania Delegation, Address List, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - Pennsylvania Delegation, Organizational Memorandum, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 34)
      - Pennsylvania Delegation, Schedule, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 35)
      - Platform Committee, Amendment Forms and Notes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Platform Committee, Diversity Memorandum, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Platform Committee, Platform Delegate List, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Platform Committee, Individual Rights and Personal Safety Plank Draft, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Platform Committee, Notes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Platform Committee, Proposed Planks sent to Hillman, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Platform Committee, Resolutions for Adoption during Orientation Meeting, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Platform Committee, Schedule of Events, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Platform Committee, Subcommittee Lists, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Platform Committee, Subcommittee on Families and Society, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Convention Calendar and Schedule, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Convention Meeting Agenda and Notes, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Delegate Phone Bank Agenda/Schedule, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Delegate Profile Sheets, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Information Packet, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Memorandum concerning Amendments in Minority Views of Platform, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Republican Coalition for Choice, Notes on Convention Activities, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Republican National Committee, Directory of Executive State Party Members, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Republican National Committee, News Releases, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Republican National Committee, Summer Meeting Agenda, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Republican National Convention, Lifetime Achievement Award, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Republican Platform, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Republican Voices for Choice, Memorandum, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Rules, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Temporary Roll of Delegates and Alternates, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Tentative Agenda and Travel Desk Details, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Thank You Notes and Letters, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Tolerance Plank, Bennett, William, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Tolerance Plank, Buchanan, Patrick, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Tolerance Plank, Center for Reproductive Law and Policy Documents, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 30)
      - Tolerance Plank, Coalition to Keep the Republican Party Pro-Life Mailing, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 31)
      - Tolerance Plank, Contact List of State Delegation Leaders and Whips, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - Tolerance Plank, Dobson, James, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 33)
      - Tolerance Plank, Governor Pete Wilson Committee, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Tolerance Plank, Letter sent to Bob Dole from Hillman, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 35)
      - Tolerance Plank, Letter sent to Bob Dole on behalf of Pennsylvania Delegation, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 36)
      - Tolerance Plank, Letters sent to Hillman in support of Tolerance Language, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 37)
      - Tolerance Plank, Letters to State Delegates regarding Platform Language, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Tolerance Plank, Letters to Tom Ridge and RNC Chairman Haley Barbour on altering Human-Life Amendment, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Tolerance Plank, Memorandum concerning declaration of tolerance on Platform, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Tolerance Plank, Memorandum concerning letter sent to Dole from Pennsylvania Delegation, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Tolerance Plank, Memorandum to Tom Ridge requesting support on Tolerance Plank, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Tolerance Plank, Notes on votes for and against Plank, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Tolerance Plank, Pennsylvania Statement of Principles Memorandum, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - Tolerance Plank, Polling Data, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
      - Tolerance Plank, Questionnaire Sent to Team 100 Members, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Tolerance Plank, Republican Governor's Association Press Release, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Tolerance Plank, Statements by George Pataki and Christine Todd Whitman, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Tolerance Plank, Statement of Principles proposed by Bob Dole and Platform Committee Chair Henry Hyde, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Tribune-Review Focus Magazine, Special Issue on Republican National Convention, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - 37th Republican National Convention, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 2000
      - Convention Maps, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Convention Newspaper, The Compassionate Patriot, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Leslie Gromis to Elsie Hillman, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence, Fred Meyer to Elsie Hillman, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Delegate Badge, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 18)
      - Delegates, Composite Listing of Congressional Districts, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Delegates, Credentials and Registration Memoranda, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Events Schedule, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 21)
      - Housing, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Invitations, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
      - The Main Street Record, Special Issue, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Memorandum, Seated Guests at Events, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Minority Report Petition on Republican Platform, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 26)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Official Delegate and Media Guide, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Official Report of the Proceedings, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 29)
      - Pennsylvania Delegation, Calendar of Events, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania Delegation, List of Delegates and Alternates, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Pennsylvania Delegation, Media Guide and Training Kit, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Breakfast Meeting Agenda, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Call Report, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 5)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Contact Information Forms for Participating Companies and Individuals, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Convention 2000 Strategy Meeting Notes (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Correspondence, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 8)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Draft of Letter to RNC and Team 100 Members, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Federal Advocacy Priorities, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Funding and Contribution Notes, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Guest Lists for Planned Events, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Handwritten List of Events and Sponsors, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Invitation (by Hillman) to Pittsburgh Presence Events, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Invitation for Reception at the Democratic National Convention, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Invitation Designs for Pittsburgh Presence Events, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Mailing List and Sample Form, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Media Coverage Guide and Press Release, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Meeting Agendas, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Memoranda, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 20)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Mobot Inc., "Adam 40-80" Overview, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Overview of Proposed Event to Promote the "New" Pittsburgh, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 22)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Pennsylvania Tech Fest Event, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 23)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Pledged Contributions and Expenses, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Project Outline Draft, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 26)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Speech Notes on Pittsburgh Presence Initiative, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Strategy Paper, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - Pittsburgh Presence, Thank you letter to Pittsburgh Regional Stakeholders, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - Program and Summary of Events, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - Republican Governor's Association Information Packet, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 31)
      - Republican Platform, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 32)
      - Republican Pro-Choice Coalition, Article Packet, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 33)
      - Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania, Convention Reporter, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 34)
      - Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania, Delegate Directory, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 35)
      - Ridge Leadership Circle, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 36)
      - Rules, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 37)
      - Seating Chart, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 38)
      - Tribute to Laura Bush, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 39)
      - The Tusk Family Visits Philadelphia, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 40)
      - Welcome Mailing from George W. Bush, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 41)
      - Welcoming Reception and Sunday Party Information, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 42)
      - WISH List Breakfast Honoring Elsie Hillman, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - WISH List Breakfast Honoring Elsie Hillman, Remarks by Hillman, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Pittsburgh and Allegheny County Republican Parties, 1939-1994; 3.
    Subseries 3 contains correspondence, memoranda, newspaper clippings, and other records pertaining to Elsie Hillman's Republican Party activities and involvement at the city and county levels. Elected as a Committee Member of the 14th Ward Republican Party, and later as Republican Chairman for the 14th Ward in 1964, Hillman was involved in various capacities in local politics, working to encourage involvement in the local Republican Party in addition to supporting local, state, and national campaigns. In 1967, she was elected Republican County Chairwoman of Allegheny County, a position she held until 1970 (Never a Spectator, 19-30).
    - 1963 Elections, Congratulatory Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Allegheny County Controller's Report, 1970 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Allegheny County Gubernatorial Survey, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Allegheny County Visitors Trip to Gubernatorial Inauguration, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Armand Taxi Cab Drivers, c.1988 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Campaign Guidelines Booklets, 1968-1970 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Candidate Screenings, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 7-9)
    - Chartiers Valley Council of Republican Women, Newspaper Clipping, c. 1990 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1963-1990 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - County Chair, Clippings, 1968-1971 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - County Chair Election, Campaign Mailings, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - County Chair Election, Clippings, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages List, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, A-B, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, C-G, 1967 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, H-L, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, M-O, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, P-S, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, T-Z, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - County Chair Election, Congratulatory Messages, unidentified, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - County Chair Election, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - County Chair Election, Thomas Geer Campaign, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - County Chair Expenses, 1967-1970 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - County Chair Re-election, Correspondence, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - County Chair Re-election, Newspaper Clippings, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - County Chair Re-election, Press Releases, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - County Chair, Retirement, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - County Committee Member, Certificate, c. 1980 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - County Committeewoman, Election Certification, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - County Committeewomen, Election Certification, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - County Committeewoman, Election Certificate, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - County Constable Elections, Newspaper Clipping, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - County Finance Committee & 500 Club, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - County Rules, 1939 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - County Rules, Revisions, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 20-21)
    - County Vice Chair Election, Clippings, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - County Vice Chair Election, Correspondence, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - County Vice Chair Election, News Release, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - County Vice Chair Election, Postponement Petitions, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Dinner honoring Mary Miano, Newspaper Clipping, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Draft Hillman Mayoral Campaign, Newspaper Clippings, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - General Elections Results, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Goldstein Tribute, Clipping, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Jobs and Recommendations, 1971 (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner, "Dinner with Ike," Clipping, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner, Elsie Hillman Recipient of the "Spirit of Lincoln Award", 1986 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Lincoln Day Dinner, Senator Richard Lugar, Guest Speaker, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Mayor Murphy Strategies Prepared for Hillman, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Memorandum, "Re: Follow-up of Election Fight", 1966 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Miller, Irwin, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Pennsylvania Women's Political Caucus of Allegheny County, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce Course on Practical Politics, Newspaper Clipping, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Primary Elections, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Reapportionment, 1971-1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Republican Citizens Committee of the United States, Critical Issues Papers, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Republican Headquarters Funding, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Republican Industry Workshops, Correspondence and Scheduling Materials, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Republican Industry Workshops, Participant Questionnaires, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Republican Nationalities Heritage Council of Allegheny County, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Republican Party of Allegheny County, Newspaper Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Rodd Report on Pittsburgh Political Scene, 1972 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Salute to Elsie Hillman Dinner, Clippings, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Salute to Elsie Hillman Dinner, Congratulatory Correspondence, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Salute to Elsie Hillman Dinner, Introduction Speech, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Salute to Elsie Hillman Dinner, Invitation, Tickets and Table Markers, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Salute to Elsie Hillman Dinner, Program, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Salute to the President Dinner, 1971 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Speech Notes, On Pittsburgh Mayoral Election, c. 1973 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Women for a Republican Congress, Campaign Ideas Booklet, 1970 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Voter Registration Materials, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania, 1967-1999; 4.
    Subseries 4 contains correspondence, memoranda, newspaper clippings, and other records pertaining to Elsie Hillman's involvement in the Republican State Committee of Pennsylvania and related political topics of interest. Hillman became a member of the Pennsylvania Republican Leadership Committee in 1974, remaining a member until 1996. Many of the records are relating to person of interest, or pertinent topic or issue.
    - Anti-Choice Dispute, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Asher, Robert, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Barbara Bush Fundraising Event, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Black Republicans, c.1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Boilermakers Dispute, c. 1970s (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Cessar, Rick, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Clarion County Republican Committee, A Tribute to Elsie Hillman, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 13-14)
    - Correspondence, 1980-1991 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Cumberland County Lincoln Day Dinner, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Delegate Selection Process Report, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Divorce Reform, c. 1978 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Dwyer, R. Budd, 1984-1986 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Gleason, Robert, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - GOP Club Memberships, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Governor's Response to State Deficit Dilemma, 1979-1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Gubernatorial Endorsement Report, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Gubernatorial Inauguration Planning, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Human Relations Commission, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Invitation to Leadership Committee, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Drew, 1977-1988 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Luksik, Peg, 1990-1994 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Meehan, Billy, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda and Meeting Minutes, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 7-9)
    - Murraysville Council of Republican Women, Speech Notes, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1980-1993 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Pamphlet, On the Responsibilities of State Chairman, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Parklands Payback Plan, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania Black Action Committee, Proposed Affirmative Action Plan for the Pennsylvania Republican Party, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Pennsylvania Environmental Issues, 1990-1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Equal Rights Amendment, Booklet on Impact, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Pennsylvania Republican Leadership League, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Pennsylvania State Mayor's Association, Article Submission, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Pike County Council of Republican Women Luncheon, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Polling Data, Hillman for Lt. Governor, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Reception for Mayor Rizzo, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Report on State Committee Structures, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Republican Finance Committee of Pennsylvania, Committee Fundamentals Overview, c. 1977 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Republican National Committee Task Force Report to State Committee, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Rules Committee, Meeting Minutes and Notes, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Senate Bill 1776, Valley Forge, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Snelling, Charles, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Speech Notes, c. 1970 -1993 (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
    - State Chair Succession, Newspaper Clippings, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - State Committee Newsletter Remarks, Women in the GOP, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - State Judicial Report, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - State Republican Leaders and County Insights, 1982 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - State Secretary of Agriculture Dispute, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Stauffer, Sarah, Obituary and Bereavement Statement, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Turrell, Ellen, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Republican Leadership Council, 1998-2000; 5.
    Subseries 5 contains correspondence, memoranda, newspaper clippings, and other records pertaining to Elsie Hillman's involvement with the Republican Leadership Council. Founded in 1993, the Republican Leadership Council was a Republican PAC focused on working to promote moderate Republican principles and candidates. It was disbanded on the national level in 2011. (Wikipedia)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Memoranda and Contributions Voucher, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1998-2000 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - RLC News Alerts, Newsletter and Brochure, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Winter Meeting Briefing Packet, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Republican Future Fund, 1993-1997; 6.
    Subseries 6 contains correspondence, mailings, memoranda, and other records relating to Elsie Hillman's involvement with the Republican Future Fund. Formed in part by Hillman in 1993, the Republican Future Fund, similar to the Republican Leadership Council was a PAC aimed at promoting moderate Republican values in Pennsylvania. Most of the material in this subseries relates to the 1994 Republican State Committee Elections.
    - Campaign Expense Report, 1996 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - List of Potential Legislative Allies, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Memoranda, 1995-1997 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Republican State Committee Elections, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 13)